Oh, hey, I'm Amanda Seals.
Once upon a time, I was in Hollywood looking at fame as something that I needed in order to live a peaceful and happy life.
Only to find out fame will absolutely prevent you from having a peaceful and happy life.
You know what gives you a peaceful and happy life?
Trees and support from folks who want everyone to have a peaceful and happy life.
So I want to shout out those folks because they exist in many places as well as on my Patreon.
And we are over there on Patreon supporting each other, teaching each other, laughing with each other,
and all the stuff that comes along with wanting this entire planet to be a peaceful and happy place.
Come on and join us.
Support a real one.